Guide to the United Automobile Workers of America, District 65 Records WAG 006
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series IX: Unprocessed Material, 1933-1995.
  - Subseries IX:D: Files of Frank Brown, 1933-1989
    - Histadrut, Florida-Histradut, Hofstra Material, Matters on Housing, Hull House EU, Illegal Alien Material, Industrial Peace National Council, International Chemical Workers Union, I.L.G.W.U., International Leather Goods Plastic and Novelty Workers Union, I.L.A., Israel Horizons, "Israel Today" Publications, Israel Bonds, Israel 1967 Crisis, undated, 1967 (Box 200)
    - Hermans, Harper & Row, Weekly Planners-4 Portfolios 1986-89, Columbia, New Organization Worksheets, undated, 1986-1989 (Box 201)
    - (7 bound portfolios) Organization Surveys, Completed Contracts, Organization Activities by Organizers, undated, 1967 (Box 202)
    - Germany Trip May '85, Givat Haviva '86-'88, Greater New York Community Labor Committee, Mark Green Campaign Mat'l '86, Greyhound Strike Mat'l '83, Hartz Mountain, Hormel Mat'l, Histadrut-National Committee for Labor Israel, Inter-Office Memos '89-'90, Jewish Affairs Committee '88-'89, Jewish Labor Committee, Jewish New Year Cards '87, Harold Krieger & Assoc., Lauderhill Medical Center-Florida, Leaflets '83-'89, Lerners/Limited Mat'l Feb '85, Liberal Party '86, Local 19 &19A, Local 28 '84, Local 259 UAW, Local 1199, Kevin Lynch '83, Mailgrams Sent '84-'85, Mailgrams Received, Major Contract Expirations '85, Mayflower Corp., Metropolitan Cap Council Election Campaign '84, Misc. Letters Sent '84, Misc. Letters Received from '83-'89, Mondale-Ferraro Election Mat'l '84, Newspaper Clippings, New York Organizing Committee '84, Old Dutch Mustard, ORT, Petrie Store Agreement (Miller-Wohl 7/31/85, Presidential Election Mat'l 11/6/84, Retirees Reachout Program, South Africa Mat'l '85-'87, undated, 1983-1989 (Box 203)
  - Subseries IX:E: Files of David Livingston, 1935-1991
    - Hiring Hall: '84; '85; '86; '87-'88; '89-'90, Hiring Hall Reports, Livingston David: Incoming Corresp. '81-'82;Outgoing Corresp. '81, '82; Outgoing Corresp. '83, '84; Incoming Corresp. '83-'84; Incoming Corresp. '85-'86; Outgoing Corresp. '85-'86; Incoming Corresp. '86; Incoming Corresp. '87; Outgoing Corresp. '87; Incoming Corresp. '88; Outgoing Corresp. '88; Incoming Corresp. '88-'89; Outgoing Corresp. '88-'89, undated, 1981-1989 (Box 204)
    - Full Employment: Gross & Moses '73, Gandhi Society for Human Rights undated; '63-'66, Garment Strike (Dist. 65) 5/73, Geotel Inc. '78, Grand Jury (Livingston Stance) '52-'53, Graphic Artists Guild undated; '75, Green Haven Prison '71-'72, Hanoi Trip undated; '54; '57; '70-'73; '89, Hanoi Trip/Vietnam:Press Coverage '71-'73; '75; '78, Harper & Row '74-'77; '81, Hartley Committee Hearings '47-'49, Hartz Mountain Corp. undated; '79;; '81-'83, Hate Mail undated; '37; '40-'41; '43; '47-'52, Health of Americans Conference '70-'71; '74, Hofstra Univ.: Dist. 65 Institute '75-'81, Hospital Settlement 7/14/60, Hospitals: Perm. Admin. Comm. undated; '58-'60; '61-'62, House Un-American Activities Comm. '64-'67, Humphrey-Hawkins Bill '77-'78, Impeachment '73-'74, Initiative Committee for National Economic Planning '75, Institute for Policy Studies '80-'81, undated, 1937-1989 (Box 205)
    - RWDSU Corresp. '54, CIO-City '46, City CIO Council '53, CIO National Office-Wash. DC, CIO (State), Committee for Astor Place, Constitution & Resolutions, Corresp. Saftey Committee Minutes, Cost of Living Council-Guidelines, Dailey, Thelma, Development & Training Center, Press Releases, undated, 1946-1953 (Box 206)
    - Pension Plan Summary, Santiago-Eddie, Solidarity, Spanish Affairs Committee, Staff Salary Policy & Other Mat'l, State Commission Against Discrimination, Store Workers Security Plan-Proposed Trust Agreement, Taft-Hartley Act, Teachers College Employees Association, Teamster-National, Teamsters Union #16, Teamsters Union Local 688, Unemployment, Union of Concerned Scientists, undated (Box 207)
    - Facts & Figures: Dist 65 13th Convention 10/20-22/72 (Portfolio), Member & Applicant Inventory (Portfolio), Miscellaneous Labor Publications and Loose Papers, Sam Katz Material, undated, Oct 20, 1972-Oct 22, 1972 (Box 208)
    - Research Dept., Resolutions (Panama-Central America), Resolution on Israel, Revlon, Sane, TOP Executive Board Meeting 4/17/91, UAW TOP Records (9 folders), Telegrams/Mailgrams, Voter Registration, Hispanic Voter Registration Drive '82, NY/DC Voting Rights Amendment, NWU Affiliation Proposal, National Writers Union, undated, 1982-1991 (Box 209)
    - United Dept. Stores, United Labor Action Committee, United Nations, URWSDEA '43-'44, URWSDEA Convention '46, URWSDEA NY Joint Council, URWSDEA Convention '42, URWSDEA Wolchok Story, Veterans Work, Village Voice, Wage Freeze-Washington Rally 10/7/72, Wage Policy, Wage Stabilization, War Labor Board, undated, 1942-1972 (Box 210)
    - Convention Reports '52, Officers Report, Correspondence '49, Portfolio (unlabeled)-w/ the following tabs: Bill Tate; Gmt. Locals; Corr.; Cleve Robinson; Jim Briggs; Milt Reverby; Out of Town; Misc., Portfolio: Comparative Inventory of Workers on the Job, Misc.: "A", Misc.: "B", Misc.: "C", Misc.: "D", Misc.: "E", undated, 1949, 1952 (Box 211)
    - Int'l Fed. Of Chem. & Gen. Workers Union '67-'80, Int'l Longshormens & Warehousemens Union '40-'54, Israel undated; '54-'79, Jenkins-Clive '73-'80, Jewelry Workers (merger) '73-'80, Johnson-Lyndon '65, Kennedy- John F. undated; '60-'83, Kennedy-Se. Edward: on Vietnam '66-'72, King Center-Atlanta '68-'80, King-M.L.: on birthday undated; '69-'78, Krieger-Harold '52-'74, Labor for Peace '72, Labor Mission to Hanoi (Nation Article) 4/24/72, Labor-University Alliance '71-'76, Legal Dept,: Don Grody '71-'73, Legal Workers (NLRB Cases) '80, Local 1199-Hospital Workers undated; '48-'72, Madison Sq. Garden Rally ("65 Story"): '51; 2/13/57; 10/21/58; 3/13/62; 10/23/63, Meeting Notices, Membership Inventories: 3/41-8/41; 10/41-12/41, Membership/Leadership Profiles '55-'62, Merger w/UOPWA '50, undated, 1941-1983 (Box 212)
    - Correspondence (5 folders): "P" & "Q" '70-'80, "R" '78-'82; '70-'77, "S" '63-'75; '76-'82, Cornell University:NYSSILR '56-'77, Credentials Committee '44, Dept. Store & Warehouse Workers Union-Local 1499 '49-'50, Distributive Worker Union Strike Relief Fund '49-'50, Dist. 65 History '52-'63, Dues Schedule '79-'81, Education '73-'81, Eagle Button Co. '80, Eisner & Levy P.C. (9 Folders) '71-'81, Elections (Dist. 65) '39-'40, Elections Committee '43-'44, Employee Retirement Income Security Act '76, Finances (2 Folders): '49-50; '74-'78, Ford-President Gerald R. (Nixon Pardon, etc.)'74-'75, undated, 1939-1982 (Box 213)
    - SANE: Nat'l Committee for a Sane Nuclear Policy '57-'75, Schlossberg-Stephen '69-'82, Scholarships '69-'81, Security Clause '47-'49, Security Plan (7 Folders): Financial Reports '78-'82; Harold Faggan '55-'80; Memos '72-'81; Pension Fund Financial Reports '77-'81; vs. Blue Cross '74-'79 '80-'82, Spain- Carabanchel Ten '73-'75, Speech: Ethical Culture Society, Speech Leadership Training, Speech: WBAI 11/17/60, Stewards Book '41, Stewards File '43-'44, Stewards List (w/ ethnic/racial info) '54, Subversive Organizations List '52, Unemployment: Dist. 65 v. Richard Nixon '45-'83, Vietnam War '66-'79, Wartime Correspondence '42-'43, Wholesales Sales Representatives (Retirement, Trust, etc.) (3 folders): '71-'78; '79, '80-'82, Wofford-Harris 11/20/59, undated, 1941- 1982 (Box 214)
    - Convention: (3 folders): '64; '65; '66, Cooper Union '73-'76, Correspondence '64-'71, Correspondence (13 folders): "F" '67-'81; "G" '68-'82; "H" '72-'80; "I" '71-'77; "J" '71-'81; "K" '65-'82; "L" '69-'81; "M" '77-'81; '67-'76; Members '70-'77; '78-'82; "N" '70-'82; "O" '73-'82, undated, 1964-1982 (Box 215)
    - Military Records '42-'46, Minimum Wage Campaign '64-'74, Montgomery Ward Organizing Committee '44-'45, NAACP '60-'76, National Conference on Public Service Employment '71, National Mobilization Against the Draft '80, NEH Proposal "Workers Look at Their Jobs and Their Union '77-'78, National Peace Action Coalition '68-'71, National Urban League '57-'58, Neuberger Shapiro Rabinowitz & Boudin '47-'50, NYC Central Labor Council '59-'81, NY County Medical Society '55, NY State Committee on Discrimination in Housing '52-'58, New York University '67-'75, No Strike Pledge '42-'45, Organizing '69, Organizing Drive '41, Organizing: Puerto Ricans '64-'65, Ossman-Arthur '42-'77, Patman Committee 4/73, Payroll '45-'46, Peekskill (incl. Robeson Letter) '49-'50, Peoples Realty Corp. '78-'81, Personal Corresp. & Papers '46-'78, Personnel Reports '41-'46, Pickover Murder: Wiz Novelty Co. '41, Poverty/Cost of Living '71-75, Practicing Law Institute '69-'71, Prepaid Legal Service '74-'75, Price Controls '42-'43, Progressive Alliance '78-'79, Publishing Division '74, Rauh-Joseph '70-'71, Reagan Budget Cuts '81, Retail Wholesale and Dept. Store Union '58-'75, Rosenzweig-Morris: Interview on History of Dist. 65 '84, Rutgers '78-'80, Rutgers University: Dist 65 Social Sciences Center, undated, 1941-1984 (Box 216)
    - Alliance for Labor Action '68-'72, Amalg. Clothing Workers '74-'81, Amalg. Meat Cutters '72-'76, Amer. Academy of Pol. & Soc. Science '74-'75, Amer. Arbitration Assoc. '47-'85, Amer. Friends of the Hebrew Univ. 10/56, Amer. Friends Service Comm. '59-'77, Amer. Jewish Cong. '64-'80, Amer. Psychol. Assoc '79-'81, Associations '53, Atlanta Murders '80-'81, Bernkopf-Al '80-'81, Bloomingdales '50-'62, Boycott of Woolworths, Brotherhood Rallies '58-'59, Building Security, Building Service Employees Int'l Union '48, Burke-Bob 1/10/75, Carter-President Jimmy '77-'79, Chambers & Chambers '35-'37, Chile, Church World Service '77, Citizens Party '80, City University of New York '73-'76, Civil Rights:General '51-'66, Columbia School of Social Work '76-'81, Comm. to Reform Judicial Selection '70, Constitution 1/44, Constit. Draft:NCDWA '70, Convention:'43; '44,; Delegates List '44; Resolutions '44; '45; '46; Corresp. '46; Greetings '46; '47; '48; Corresp. '48; Greetings '48; 4/19/53; '54; Delegate List '54; Greetings '54; '58; '62, undated, 1935-1981 (Box 217)
    - Army File '46, Livingston Correspondence (not personal) '49, Transcription of Exec. Council Mtg. 10/7/60, Martin Luther King Letter 9/16/60, Convention Reports '54, Guests & Invitations 10/60 Conf., Dist 65 8th Biennial Convention 9/26-28/58, Elections/Nominations '58, Dist 65 Biennial Convention 10/7-9/60, Convention '56, 7th Biennial Convention 5/11-13/56, undated, 1946-1960 (Box 218)
    - Miscellaneous Labor Publications and Loose Papers, 5 Portfolios: Legal Services-UAW CAP Directors 3/14/81; New Jersey Region Organization Targets; Worker Inventory; Completed Contracts '69-'74; Statistics for Dist. 65 Convention 9/62, undated, 1962-1981 (Box 219)
    - Convention '62, Convention Report '62, Convention Report: Cleve Robinson '69, Convention Press Coverage '69, Convention Reports '69, Dist 65. Convention Agenda 10/20/72, Dist. 65 Convention 10/18-22/72, undated, 1962-1972 (Box 220)
    - Weisman Cellar Etc., John Wiley & Sons, Womens Committee, "Tighten Up Our Fighting Arm" Arthur Osman, Local 65 Biennial Convention 5/24-25/46, Local 65 3rd Biennial Convention 5/29-31/48, Local 65 4th Biennial Convention 1950, Founding Convention DWU 2/4-5/50, DPOWA National Executive Board 4/12-14/51, Local 65 5th Biennial Convention 5/17-18/52, undated, 1946-1952 (Box 221)
    - Persian Gulf Info Package, Disarmament Rally 6/12/82, Newspaper-Krupat, Teamsters Local 840, Dist. 65 Stewards & LOs Negotiating Committee, Clerical: re S.P. Arbitration, Personnel- Seniority List '91, Caffee/Holmes/Ortiz, Puerto Rico-Ralph Rivera, Puerto Rico, Puerto Rico-Figures, Puerto Rican Legal Defense Fund, Puert Rican Legal Defense & Education Fund, Princeton-NJ, undated, 1982-1991 (Box 222)
    - Education Conference-Tisch Hall NYU 12/10/82, Members Assistance Program, Reach-Out, Human Services-Security Plan: Beth Silverman, Yale Decision, United Mine Workers, Jack Paley, Comptrollers Office-M. Rosenzweig, Consumer Service, Contract Dept.-P. Manheim, Employment Office-J. Tillman, Finance Dept., "A", "B", "C", "D", "E", "F", "G", "H", "J", "K", "L", "M", Messina-Al, "P", "Q", "R", "S", "T", "U", "V", "W-X", "Y-Z", undated, 1982 (Box 223)
    - Hermans, Housing Now, New Immigration Law, Immigration Testimony 10/30/89, Testimony re: IRCA Employer Sanctions, National Labor Committee in Support of El Salvador, Lerner Shops, Lerners, Local 26, Memphis, Local #28 (Featherston & Hildred) Charlotte NC, Local #28 (Harry Bush), Memo re: 1199 & Dist. 65, Hospital Workers 1199, Central America Committee, Mandela's US Tour 6/20-22/90, South Africa, Labor for Peace-Gulf Crisis, Solidarity Day, March on Washington-25th Anniversary Celebration, April 25th Demonstration in Washington DC, 20th Anniversary Mobilization-March on Washington 8/27/83, Mobilization-Special Unity Period 8/27/83 & Labor Day '83, Jobs w/Justice/Healthcare, Jobs w/ Peace, US Out of Central America, NY Area Committee in Support of Democracy, Solidarity Day: Washington DC 8/31/91, undated, 1983-1991 (Box 224)
  - Subseries IX:F: Files of Roger Keeran, 1981-1984
    - Adult Education-General, Articles, Bergen, "C", Camden, Cincinnati-Revlon, Clipping Articles for NJ College Program, Club, Convention-New Jersey '81, Course Outlines, Cornell, Cumberland County College, Curriculum, Curriculum Worksheet, Day File, Education Committee, Education Fund, Faculty Meeting, Field Study '83-'84, Forth Wall Repertory Theater, Foster, "G", GED, History: Dist. 65, Hofstra University, undated, 1981-1984 (Box 225)
    - Institute for Labor Education & Research, Institute for Labor Educ. & Research: Theories Course, Job Training & Upgrading, "K", Labor Research Association, Learning Unlimited, Livingston, "M", Marc Mappen, March on Washington '83, Mendez-Renee: Meetings with, Middlesex, New Members Class, Newsletter, New York-General, Officer Training, OSHA, Organizing, "P", Peace, Peer Counseling, Questionnaires/Applications, "R", undated, 1983 (Box 226)
    - Recommendations, Recruitment-Dist 65/RU, Roberts-Leslie, Reverby-Milton, Ramapo College Material, Rutgers University Labor Educ. Center (6 folders): Out-of-State; Non-Credit; Dean Nanry; New Brunswick; Rutger Labor Ed. Ctr.; Program of ASS, "S", Secretary, Staff Meetings, Stewards School, Student Affairs, Student Questionnaire '84, Student Reps, Students-Current, Study Skills, Sylvia, "T", UE Education, UAW Education, Unemployment, "W", undated, 1984 (Box 227)
  - Subseries IX:G: Negotiation Files
    - Hartz-Mountain (3 expandable file folders): Bargaining Notes/Trial Exhibits; NLRB Exhibits/Historical Material; Decision Briefs/Recent Correspondence, undated (Box 228)
    - Washington Business Institute, YALDAYNU '86, Club Med, undated, 1986 (Box 229)
  - Subseries IX:H: UAW Merger 1982-1987
    - Correspondence-Doug Fraser, UAW Merger Correspondence, Background Material 11/83, United Automobile Workers, Owen Biebers Remarks at General Council Meeting 6/29/83, Articles/Bieber 11/83, Livingston/Shoemaker Meeting: Detroit 9/6/85, UAW Meeting with Bieber 10/3/85, undated, 1982-1987 (Box 230)
  - Subseries IX:I: Writings of Milton Reverby, 1970-1973
    - Portfolio Exhibits 1-40 (2 binders), "Racism in the Labor Movement: A Perspective", Visions, of the Underground Press (1970 annual issue), "Portfolio: Review of My Life and Work Experiences (submitted to Empire State College: Grad 1973), undated, 1970-1973 (Box 231)
  - Subseries IX:J: National Labor Relation Board
    - Expandable File, A-Z, undated (Box 232)
  - Subseries IX:K: Shop Files (folders arranged alphabetically by shop name)
    - AA Plastics-A&E Sac through "Columbia University Bookstore", undated (Box 233)
    - Comar-Concord Plastics through "Hahnes-Victor B. Handel", undated (Box 234)
    - Handler through "Knickerbocker-Knight Litho", undated (Box 235)
    - Knit Studio Fabric Center through "Ming Art, Inc.", undated (Box 236)
    - Mergenthaler Linotype, undated (Box 237)
    - E. Mishan & Sons through "Premier Albums (SMG Sound Course), undated (Box 238)
    - Prentice Hall through "Silco Knitting Mills", undated (Box 239)
    - Silver Thermal through "A.Weinman Co. Inc", undated (Box 240)
    - Samuel Weiser Book Store through "John Wiley & Sons", (continues with files of locals and labor workers from other states): Bob Burke-Local 66 (Calif.), Harry Bush (Fla.), Erskine Hepburn (Fla.), Iva Groover-Local 605 (Tallahassee, Fla.), Elvira Haywood Local 1010 (St. Petersburg, Fla.), Robert Keyes Local 27A (Newport News, Va.), Maryanne Massenberg (Calif.), Dist. 65 Region 9 (Puerto Rico), undated (Box 241)
  - Subseries IX:L: Miscellaneous Files, 1956-1994
    - Teachers Union, Teamsters (NY and locals from areas other than NJ), Teamsters (NJ area), International Brotherhood of Teamsters, IBT: Correspondence & Local 813, IBT: Local 810 & Greenwald, IBT: Constitution/By-Laws & Misc. IBT Publications, Local 806 JBT, Textile Associations, Textile Workers Union, Tourist Industry Development, Training Program, Transport Workers Union of America, Travel Literature (EL-AL Airlines), Typographical Union, undated (Box 242)
    - Misc. Reports, Local 1199 Reports, Dist 65 Income Tax, Theft Loss 8/25/66, D.P.O. & Dist. Realty, Memorandums '72-'74, Tom Mooney Hall, Leaflets from "65" Shop Files, undated, 1966-1974 (Box 243)
    - Consumer Service, Domestic Merchandising Corp.: Financial Reports, Distributive Realty Corporation: Financial Reports, The District 65 Education Fund: Financial Reports, Local 2, Tom Mooney Hall Association, Inc: Financial Reports, undated (Box 244)
    - Budget Reports, 65 General Fund, Payroll Memos, UAW Corresp., General Corresp., General Council Meeting Minutes '77, Dist. 65 Finance Department Report on Organizational Activities, Morris Rosenzweig Reports, Training Program Audit Report 12/5/77-1/25/78, Development & Training Center, Credit Union, Security Plan Pension Fund re: ERISA, Analysis of Old-time Textile Workers re: Pension Credits, Jewish Affairs, Appraisals-13 Astor Place, Mortgage-13 Astor Place, Correspondence-Chemical Corn Exchange re: Loan & Mortgage on Building, Estimated Replacement Appraisal of Building & Contents 2/59, Old Financial Reports, Tom Mooney Hall, TMHA Room Rentals, Tom Mooney Hall-Board of Directors Meeting, Tom Mooney Hall Association, undated, 1959-1978 (Box 245)
    - National Council of the Distributive Workers of America, DWA Exec. Board Mtgs: 4/8-10/73 (Tamiment); 4/11-12/75, DWA Exec. Board & Convention: 4/23-24/76; 4/15-16/77; '78, Sindicato Obrero Insular, National Council: List of Contracts, Local 19, Local 26, Local 28, Local 30: Detroit MI, Retail Store Employees Local 230-Montreal, Plastic & Novelty Workers-St. Louis, Local 201:St. Louis MO, Local 103A: University of Chicago, Encyclopedia Britannica, Boston Local, Lerners: Texas & L.A. Calif., Lerners: Chicago & Pittsburgh, Leslie Roberts-Atlanta, Charleston-N.C.D.W.A., Columbus GA, undated, 1973-1978 (Box 246)
    - DWA Exec. Board Mtg: 7/79, DWA '79, DWA Exec. Board Mtg. 4/15-16/77: Corresp., DWA Exec. Bd. Mtg. 4/23/76, Changes in Constitution of DWA, Constitution-Attn: Morris Rosenzweig, DWA Convention 4/23-24/76, DWA Convention: Financial Reports 4/24/76, Balloting for Delegates to DWA Convention 4/24/76, DWA Exec. Bd. Mtg. 4/11-12/75, DWA Convention: 6/28-29/74, DWA Exec. Bd. Mtg. 12/12/73, DWA Convention: 4/19-20/72 (proceedings & reports), DWA Financial Statements 5/31/75, DWA Financial Reports, Amalgamated Clothing & RWDSU Staff Retirement Plan, DWA Financial Statements, Exec. Comm. Mtg. Minutes(8 folders): '76; '77; '78; '79; '80; '81; '82; undated, Minutes of Exec. Comm. Meetings 9/29/65-7/16/68, Dist. 65-Miscellaneous, undated, 1965-1982 (Box 247)
    - Rally for Full Employment 9/7/77, Economic Wage Stabilization Act '71, Washington DC Meeting 10/7/71, Martin Luther King Jr. Memorial Meeting '71-'75, Israel-Munich Stoppage Mtg. 9/12/72; Israel Emergency Mtg. 10/16/73; Telegrams re: Maalot Statement-AFL-CIO, Out of Town Conference 12/3-5/74, Meeting of Unemployed-Washington DC 1/29/75, Knitwear Contractors & Unorganized Shops; Misc. Organizing Material., Direct Mail Assignments, Volunteer Organizing Corp. Material., Convention Statistics-'62, Convention Reports: '56-'69, Convention: Laurels Country Club-3/19-23/69, Targets for Organization, DWA Convention 10/18-22/72, DWA Convention Material: Cooper Union 11/13/76, NY Regional Convention 4/16-18/82, undated, 1956-1982 (Box 248)
    - Tara Reale v. D 65 Security Plan, Allstate Insurance v. D 65 Security Plan, D 65 Security and Pension plan files, D 65 Security Plan v. Graduate Platics Company Inc/Stotter (case research, notes, correspondence, and legal docs), 1990-1993 (Box 251)
    - Stotter Division of Graduate Plastics v. D 65: Arbitration, appeals, court decision, correspondence, legal documents, "plant closing", arbitrations, 1991-1994 (Box 252)
    - D. 65 versus: Otagiri Mercantile, Allerton Press, TCI, Revlon, Columbia UniversityD. 65 and: American Trim Products, Irving Berlin, Prenctice Hall, S&J Toiletries, ADEMCO, Associated Day Care of BostonIn re CardisNegotiations, arbitrations, cases, legal, pension agreements, severance, etc, 1986-1992 (Box 253)
    - D. 65 and Hartz Mountain Corporation: 1987 Transcripts, 1989 Briefs to 3rd Circuit"Box 3 of 3", 1987-1989 (Box 254)
    - D. 65 versus: UFI Razor Blades, Harper and Row, National Shoe, Nestle Lemur, Shop VacD. 65 and LaSalle: plant removal, agreements, notes on meetingsNegotiations, arbitrations, legal, etc.ACLU Contract, 1979, 1983-1988 (Box 255)
    - Feminist Press, Miscellaneous, Thelma Daily pension plan, Franklin Textile (arbitration, briefs, settlement, etc), H. G. Toys (arbitrations, etc), Harrogate Nursing home, 1978-1982 (Box 256)
    - Hartz Mountain: new charges, correspondence, arbitrations, grievances, legal, etc, 1985-1990 (Box 257)
    - D. 65 v. Hartz Mountain: 3rd Circuit Appeal, Decision, Appendix, Briefs, Exceptions, Research, Legal, etc., 1988-1990 (Box 258)
    - Arbitrations, grievances, legal, negotiations, etc:Copperstate Rubber of Arizona, Louis Chock, Adv. Air Work, Princeton University Store, Golden Eagle Mutual Life Insurance, Penguin USA, South Jersey Glass, etc, 1988-1991 (Box 259)
    - Negotiations, Arbitrations, agreements, legal, grievances, severance, pensions etc:National Lawyers Guild, Columbia, Alpha Wire Core, ADEMCO, Hofstra, Revlon, etc, 1987-1993 (Box 260)
    - Negotiations, Arbitrations, agreements, legal, grievances, severance, pensions etc:Union Theological Seminary, Revlon, Loews, etc.Dist. 65 Trustees meetings: Pension Plan fund, agreements, declaration of trust, security plans, minutes, 1985, 1991-1992 (Box 261)
    - Boston University and Northwestern University strike documents, 1978-1984 (Box 261, Box Shared Tamiment 004)
    - Videos: Eye Opener #6-"Fast Track: Trade Trap," "Broken Promise", undated (Box Shared Tamiment 013)
    - Videos: Eye Opener and Earl Robinson, Eye Opener Campaign '96, Eye Opener #3, Eye Opener One Day Longer, In the Shadow of the Tower, 1994-1998 (Box Shared Tamiment 015)